https://www.altrinchamgarrick.co.uk/info/gdpr-privacy-policy/

Home» Downloadable Documentation » GDPR Privacy Policy
EmailFacebookTwitter
The Altrincham Garrick Playhouse Privacy Policy
Altrincham Garrick Playhouse is committed to protecting personal information. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information we collect.
Our Privacy Policy relates broadly to these groups of people:
Audience: the people who attend our shows, visiting shows and events and/or have requested information about the theatre
Members: people who pay to become/be a member of the Altrincham Garrick Society
Supporters: people who are not members but are supporting the activities of the Society in a particular way. This involvement may include, but is not limited to: scenery construction; costumes; properties; make-up and hair; publicity; front of house; backstage; administration; website; design; technical; directing; sponsorship; donations; consultants; those giving specialist advice to the Altrincham Garrick.
Staff: those employed by Altrincham Garrick
Suppliers: organisations and businesses that provide goods or services to the theatre
Committees: Board of Trustees, Volunteers and Members Committee, Play Selection and Casting Committee
GAPA Members: members of Garrick Academy of Performing Arts and their parents/guardians/carers
The personal information we collect from you
Audience: Our email database contains your name and email address. Our box office contains your name, address, email address and telephone numbers so we can contact you with information relating to Altrincham Garrick only. We may hold details on previous bookings, group bookings and any preferences you may share with us.
Members: Our membership database contains your name, address, phone number/s, email address and data on your membership preferences. We also hold information on dates joined, renewals and details on payments and your membership. If you have chosen to pay by standing order or joined our 200 club we will hold those details for processing purposes only.
Supporters: We collect basic information such as name, address, telephone number, email address, quotes, emails.
Staff: We hold details of your name, address, phone number email address, National Insurance, tax details, payslips and employment history.
Suppliers: We collect basic information such as name, address, telephone number, email address, quotes, emails.
Committees: We collect basic information such as name, address, telephone number, email address, quotes, emails. For the Board of Trustees, information is also held at Companies House and with the Charity Commission, in line with legal requirements.
GAPA Members: We hold basic information such as name, address, telephone number, email address.
How we use information and data
Audience: We will send you regular bulletins via email with news about the theatre and our shows and other shows and events that appear at the theatre. There is an ‘unsubscribe’ option on every email. We will perform some basic interrogation of our email statistics, such as open-rates and click-through rates via various software. Members, group bookers and ticket holders may receive limited further information by post and email from time to time. We may contact you by telephone if there is problem with tickets or changes to a performance you are booked to attend. We will not share your information with any third parties without your consent.
Members: We will use your information to send you newsletters, letters or emails to give you details of General Meetings, shows, rehearsals, production meetings, casting, news from meetings and general events that are likely to be of interest to you. Your name, and possibly photograph and biography may appear in newsletters or show programmes, website or other publicity relating to a production you are involved in. Your information may be shared with committee members, staff and heads of departments for use in ‘legitimate interest’ and in line with GDPR regulations. Please be aware that our show programmes, website and publicity are public documents and that our newsletters are shared with other members and supporters of the theatre. We will not share your information with other third parties without your consent.
Supporters: We will use your information as and when required to contact you for Garrick matters related to your involvement with us. We will not share your information with other third parties without your consent.
Staff: We will use your information as and when required to contact you for Garrick matters related to your involvement with the Garrick and as your employer. We will not share your information with other third parties without your consent. Any personal data relating to your employment will be protected and limited to those involved to line management, Board of Trustees and for payroll purposes.
Suppliers: We will use your information as and when required to contact you for Garrick matters related to your involvement with the Garrick. We will not share your information with other third parties without your consent.
Committees: We will use your information as and when required to contact you for Garrick matters related to your involvement with the Garrick. We will not share your information with other third parties without your consent.
GAPA Members: We will use your information as and when required to contact you for Garrick Academy of Performing Arts such as subscriptions, rehearsals, summer school, productions, ticket offers, newsletters, auditions, changes of dates, nominations. Under 18s will be contacted via their parents. We will not share your information with other third parties without your consent. Your name, and possibly photograph and biography may appear in newsletters or show programmes, website or other publicity relating to a production you are involved in. Your information may be shared with committee members, staff and heads of departments for use in ?legitimate interest? and in line with GDPR regulations. Please be aware that our show programmes, website and publicity are public documents and that our newsletters are shared with other members and supporters of the theatre. We will not share your information with other third parties without your consent.
How we use information held by our Box Office Systems
The Box office at Altrincham Garrick process tickets and sales by telephone, by email, by post and in person. Processing tickets may display your name, address, email address and telephone number. For reporting purposes, we may interrogate data held in the box office to inform our business planning but personal data will not be shared with any third parties. We may hold your personal details in our records in case we need to contact you with further information if there is a change to performance details, for example.
Tickets booked via the website are linked to Tickets.com. You can find details of their Privacy Policy here.
Security
We put in place reasonable security measures to protect against any unauthorised access or damage to, or disclosure or loss of, your information
Your Rights:
Audience, Members, Supporters, Staff, Committees and GAPA
Please let us know if your information changes as it is important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date.
You have the right to request a copy of all the information we hold about you in a Subject Access Request. To do this, simply write to us at the address below. We will take all reasonable steps to confirm your identity before providing you with details of any information we may hold about you. You can ask us to remove your information from our records at any time and cease any further communication. You can do this by writing to the address below.
Members, Supporters, Committees and GAPA
We will keep your information indefinitely after you remain an active Member, Supporter, sit on a Committee or are a member of GAPA. We keep your information because you may resume your connection with and take part again in our activities. However, you can ask us to remove your information from our records at any time and we will do so and stop sending you any further communications. You can do this by writing to the address below.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time; for example, to keep it up to date or to comply with legal requirements. If there will be any significant changes made to the use of your information in a manner different from that stated, we will seek your permission first.
How to Contact Us
For any questions or concerns relating to this Privacy Policy or our data protection practices, or to make a Subject Access Request, please contact us in one of these ways:
By email admin@altrinchamgarrick.co.uk
By post
Operations Director
Altrincham Garrick Theatre
Barrington Road
Altrincham
WA14 1HZ
This page was updated on 12 October 2020.
